Understand Nifty Bank Jain, which
stocks do you hold today Harsh D Good morning Ashish, let's
start with the numbers, with this
Lombard and yesterday we saw that there was a lot of
action in the futures market
and here if you look at it, the
profit that came in is a little better than expected,
although the combine ratio is still on the
higher side and there was an increase in the net on premium
but it is
not meeting the expectations, along with the claim
ratio because some claims in the motor segment are
bigger, so that claim ratio has
increased from 72% to 74%, so the GDP
which we say is 4977 crores, there is a 650%
increase in the net on premium, there is an increase of about 12%,
3726 crores and the profit after
tax has been seen increasing by about 40%, the
combine ratio is around 104,
although the company is still saying that it will be
around 102 to 25, so these are the
highlights of ICC Lombard, now on the other hand, there are
also numbers of 18 coffees  And here
we have seen that there is an
increase of almost 20% in profit capability, about Rs 49
crore or the figure is 10% bigger in revenue,
realization has improved a little in the 8
O'Clock Coffee and Instant Coffee
segment, that is why the revenue
got some support, but there is pressure on profit, about
4%, the profit was seen sliding, this figure of 4 to
5% Rs
105 crore came, here the
volumes are a little lower and
it was visible on the input cost, so
you have to keep this in mind also, the margin is around 14 and a half
percent, in plantation business the
revenue is going up to 8%, but
some pressure is visible on profit capability
and there is an
increase of 11% in revenue in value added products and a
decline of 5 percent in profits, these are the numbers of Tata Coffee
and prices of instant coffee are again
trading at high speed,
from there also you have to monitor the stock, you were
also reading the lines, in fact the government has imposed tax
on diesel exports.  It has been reduced to
zero, just like it was on petrol,
but the
government is imposing a tax of ₹6400 on domestic crude oil production. If we
talk about some of the former companies, Zydis
Live has actually received approval from the US FDA
for its Estroyl Transmission System, which is primarily
a drug to prevent osteoporosis. Now,
its market size is around $1.9 million,
and this company will
manufacture the drug in its Muria unit in Ahmedabad. On
the other hand, Parimal Pharma has completed the US
FDA inspection at its Sales & Well
manufacturing facility. If you have received it,
you will keep that stock as well.
Prestige State has recently made a small
acquisition of around Rs 66 crore. They have invested in it.
This is a spectacular tech park. They are
acquiring it and are taking 51% stake in it.
National's primary business development and
construction activities are office space and
commercial office space. So
keep that stock also in the FOX today. All the companies
today's events calendar.  The
penultimate session will be held at 10:30 am.
Cabinet Meet I am Sir Laxman will be on it. The
website or management is not responsible for this.
Money Control advises users to
seek advice from a certified expert before taking any investment decision.